moments after a viewer asked me to kill
someone I was summoned to a meeting with
my producer Grant and reviews legal
council there should have been three
vetos yes in retrospect that is clear
but
alas anyway I just wanted to make our
position very
clear you should not commit a murder for
the show
period I agree with
that we don't care that it might have
been ground breaking award-winning
television that people might have talked
about for years none of that matters
talking about a human life that's yeah
that's right it's a human life even if
that means Fading Into Obscurity there
is no one whose life is so worthless
that you should do this yeah even if by
not doing it eventually people go oh
yeah who was that guy back in the day
Frosty mcnell he had a show where he
barfed up
pancakes and if you did do this thing
you would be doing it knowing that not
only were you not told to by the show
you were expressly told not to do
it
w
okay right good yeah okay yeah I I got
it I get it so you you're telling me
uh I I have to do this no all absolutely
not don't do it got it
okay thank you Forest yeah no thank you
very good
yeah is he going to do
it we have told him not to do
[Music]
it